{
    "id": "7db91adde9034d148aed1cae122bf439",
    "title": "Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………. finished the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "am"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ……………….. your lunch?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eat",
                "ate",
                "eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has not return",
                "is not returned",
                "has not returned"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… such a mess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never saw",
                "have never seen",
                "have never saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. he brought his violin?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Is",
                "Has",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever …………………. to Australia?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "being",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… all the plays of Shakespeare.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "am read",
                "have read"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents ...................... me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has never hurt",
                "have never hurt",
                "have never hurted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... always wanted to be a soldier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. to anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never apologized",
                "has never apologized",
                "have never apologized"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}